{"slug": "A_Study_in_Scarlet_Arthur_Conan_Doyle", "status": "error", "error": "[E050] Can't find model 'en_core_web_sm'. It doesn't seem to be a Python package or a valid path to a data directory."}
{"slug": "A_Study_in_Scarlet_Arthur_Conan_Doyle", "title": "A Study in Scarlet Arthur Conan Doyle", "language": "en", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 56109, "n_unique_entities": 61, "n_entity_mentions": 621, "sigma": 140.2725, "target_scenes": 18, "detected_scene_boundaries": [2136.5486111111113, 4869.142045454546, 7370.0259740259735, 9034.139610389611, 10606.482467532467, 12525.893452380953, 14891.084429824561, 17366.949013157893, 19964.495923913044, 22881.07670221493, 25547.63142485361, 27362.810344827587, 30855.170114942528, 36070.408771929826, 40487.87781954887, 44247.874423963134, 46596.838709677424, 48542.0, 51502.18, 54259.54], "n_scenes": 21, "top_entities": [{"label": "holmes", "count": 80, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "drebber", "count": 51, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "lestrade", "count": 47, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "gregson", "count": 41, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "stangerson", "count": 34, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "jefferson hope", "count": 34, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "john ferrier", "count": 22, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "ferrier", "count": 20, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "lucy", "count": 19, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "london", "count": 13, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "sherlock holmes", "count": 13, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "stamford", "count": 11, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "mormon", "count": 11, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "joseph stangerson", "count": 10, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "utah", "count": 9, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "the brixton road", "count": 9, "type": "FAC"}, {"label": "cleveland", "count": 9, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "lucy ferrier", "count": 9, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "mormons", "count": 9, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "german", "count": 8, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "salt lake city", "count": 8, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "afghanistan", "count": 7, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "charpentier", "count": 7, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "scotland yard", "count": 6, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "american", "count": 6, "type": "NORP"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 24727.937968984494, "activity": 0.04439428491075563}, {"token": 20601.936968484242, "activity": 0.03522291162501436}, {"token": 11816.64232116058, "activity": 0.02932530923928416}, {"token": 46115.77988994497, "activity": 0.028405090804515924}, {"token": 21977.270635317658, "activity": 0.027742344651751898}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 21, "edges": 192, "scene_entity_counts": [10, 6, 5, 7, 7, 11, 8, 10, 8, 24, 16, 7, 13, 16, 22, 11, 11, 15, 12, 19, 15]}, "elapsed_s": 5.82}
{"slug": "Le_Fantôme_de_lOpéra_Gaston_Leroux", "title": "Le Fantôme de lOpéra Gaston Leroux", "language": "fr", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 138989, "n_unique_entities": 174, "n_entity_mentions": 3417, "sigma": 347.4725, "target_scenes": 46, "detected_scene_boundaries": [2434.161206896552, 5035.066935483871, 7128.543883535818, 9265.310281385282, 12234.991210045662, 15763.552153820763, 19297.604991394146, 22407.40852130326, 25101.501594896334, 27439.663101604277, 29238.710543233687, 32443.58115908566, 36789.40130638906, 39652.73321891686, 41956.303743513716, 44899.291260382815, 48083.589113072725, 51416.1284527285, 56108.68036529681, 60313.56497175142, 63645.148305084746, 67315.38, 70897.84176470588, 74271.58319327731, 78007.53961038962, 80951.39690522244, 83409.82973350526, 86565.96994213984, 89582.00295265739, 92063.40544918999, 94447.23571428572, 97785.96428571429, 101197.38, 104679.33918367347, 108177.73596938775, 110613.25892857142, 112483.97305194805, 114826.85340909091, 117484.42916666667, 120044.77878787878, 123290.99935525467, 126846.30390070923, 129278.47179487179, 132767.2349447189, 136566.26129799522], "n_scenes": 46, "top_entities": [{"label": "raoul", "count": 391, "type": "PER"}, {"label": "christine", "count": 383, "type": "MISC"}, {"label": "erik", "count": 251, "type": "PER"}, {"label": "persan", "count": 169, "type": "MISC"}, {"label": "richard", "count": 150, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "opéra", "count": 137, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "moncharmin", "count": 114, "type": "PER"}, {"label": "christine daaé", "count": 112, "type": "PER"}, {"label": "carlotta", "count": 60, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "m.", "count": 50, "type": "PER"}, {"label": "poligny", "count": 49, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "--je", "count": 37, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "mame giry", "count": 37, "type": "PER"}, {"label": "lac", "count": 35, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "sorelli", "count": 34, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "mercier", "count": 33, "type": "PER"}, {"label": "chagny", "count": 32, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "gabriel", "count": 32, "type": "PER"}, {"label": "valérius", "count": 32, "type": "PER"}, {"label": "m. de chagny", "count": 32, "type": "PER"}, {"label": "mm. debienne", "count": 31, "type": "PER"}, {"label": "vicomte de chagny", "count": 31, "type": "PER"}, {"label": "giry", "count": 31, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "daaé", "count": 31, "type": "MISC"}, {"label": "mme giry", "count": 28, "type": "PER"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 79819.02151075538, "activity": 0.05099086035661807}, {"token": 20928.15807903952, "activity": 0.04999704642354873}, {"token": 87814.82941470736, "activity": 0.04890653237078075}, {"token": 84755.56378189095, "activity": 0.047149451220588154}, {"token": 134538.15907953976, "activity": 0.04587878696744094}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 46, "edges": 874, "scene_entity_counts": [31, 10, 19, 24, 18, 24, 31, 29, 27, 19, 7, 18, 35, 31, 16, 26, 18, 20, 28, 12, 18, 16, 23, 22, 33, 33, 35, 26, 28, 35, 26, 22, 13, 19, 24, 16, 21, 15, 16, 18, 13, 21, 16, 29, 42, 25]}, "elapsed_s": 14.49}
{"slug": "A_Honeymoon_in_Space_George_Chetwynd_Griffith", "title": "A Honeymoon in Space George Chetwynd Griffith", "language": "en", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 83194, "n_unique_entities": 77, "n_entity_mentions": 1642, "sigma": 207.985, "target_scenes": 27, "detected_scene_boundaries": [2256.2053571428573, 6116.600198412699, 8524.497782446311, 9670.86856617647, 12077.140625, 15204.939393939394, 17208.466179653682, 19242.576785714286, 21695.64523809524, 23908.62932900433, 26204.947134387352, 28163.086956521736, 30784.598913043475, 34008.212499999994, 36599.36377118644, 40049.76271186441, 43834.96644067796, 46643.56431372549, 49272.88431372549, 52165.16818181818, 54735.93326118326, 57002.76671870934, 60451.828109932496, 63893.00054466231, 66031.67056530213, 68210.37556099551, 71293.77906976745, 74687.36764705883, 77732.96098039215, 80782.02302083332], "n_scenes": 31, "top_entities": [{"label": "zaidie", "count": 280, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "astronef", "count": 221, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "redgrave", "count": 221, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "earth", "count": 82, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "van stuyler", "count": 55, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "murgatroyd", "count": 53, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "lenox", "count": 48, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "sun", "count": 47, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "mars", "count": 41, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "venus", "count": 41, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "martian", "count": 40, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "jupiter", "count": 37, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "space", "count": 29, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "washington", "count": 23, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "new york", "count": 23, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "ganymede", "count": 21, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "american", "count": 20, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "st. louis", "count": 17, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "rennick", "count": 17, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "andrew", "count": 15, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "the r. force", "count": 14, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "atlantic", "count": 13, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "mercury", "count": 13, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "the solar system", "count": 11, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "moon", "count": 11, "type": "PERSON"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 16064.281140570283, "activity": 0.04448784697303388}, {"token": 67295.18809404701, "activity": 0.04143718745810875}, {"token": 55434.25512756378, "activity": 0.041073206825932136}, {"token": 50897.96848424212, "activity": 0.040430034121325134}, {"token": 82693.59229614807, "activity": 0.039117454445801704}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 31, "edges": 423, "scene_entity_counts": [9, 27, 14, 14, 12, 19, 25, 25, 13, 11, 19, 6, 6, 12, 15, 16, 17, 17, 15, 19, 13, 19, 20, 17, 13, 20, 15, 14, 17, 17, 24]}, "elapsed_s": 7.58}
{"slug": "A_Journey_to_the_Centre_of_the_Earth_Jules_Verne", "title": "A Journey to the Centre of the Earth Jules Verne", "language": "en", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 110751, "n_unique_entities": 60, "n_entity_mentions": 696, "sigma": 276.8775, "target_scenes": 36, "detected_scene_boundaries": [1784.275, 3020.6388888888887, 4907.275252525253, 7098.136363636364, 9412.904761904761, 11995.953542392566, 13909.936280487804, 16877.114772727273, 21022.699494949495, 23636.83760683761, 25540.590384615385, 27629.867857142857, 29792.470443349754, 32060.00615763547, 34493.92857142857, 37613.75, 41449.5, 45034.57142857143, 48335.47767857143, 51208.90625, 53232.25, 55829.25, 58573.625, 61821.267857142855, 65613.14285714286, 69176.25, 72812.97727272726, 75220.8606060606, 77860.88333333333, 81332.7794117647, 84216.07941176472, 88145.55, 91842.475, 94481.975, 97657.2, 100991.7, 103871.27272727274, 105888.22727272726, 107996.29383116882], "n_scenes": 40, "top_entities": [{"label": "hans", "count": 151, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "iceland", "count": 45, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "harry", "count": 43, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "sneffels", "count": 32, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "hardwigg", "count": 30, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "uncle", "count": 27, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "saknussemm", "count": 25, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "reykjavik", "count": 19, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "icelandic", "count": 17, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "danish", "count": 15, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "hamburg", "count": 14, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "m. fridriksson", "count": 14, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "gretchen", "count": 13, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "icelander", "count": 13, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "french", "count": 10, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "henry", "count": 10, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "stapi", "count": 10, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "england", "count": 9, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "port gretchen", "count": 9, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "scartaris", "count": 8, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "german", "count": 8, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "arne saknussemm", "count": 8, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "humphry davy", "count": 7, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "latin", "count": 7, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "earth", "count": 7, "type": "LOC"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 14404.702351175587, "activity": 0.021448670547237064}, {"token": 12631.815907953976, "activity": 0.020548740969646536}, {"token": 31302.526263131564, "activity": 0.01774933437994718}, {"token": 109697.34867433716, "activity": 0.017290676745270524}, {"token": 8088.794397198599, "activity": 0.0170845043979124}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 40, "edges": 310, "scene_entity_counts": [10, 6, 9, 7, 10, 10, 18, 17, 19, 10, 10, 10, 6, 14, 9, 11, 9, 10, 5, 11, 6, 9, 5, 4, 12, 7, 8, 2, 6, 9, 12, 11, 11, 10, 4, 5, 8, 7, 4, 19]}, "elapsed_s": 9.4}
{"slug": "A_Romance_of_Billy-Goat_Hill_Alice_Caldwell_Hegan_Rice", "title": "A Romance of Billy-Goat Hill Alice Caldwell Hegan Rice", "language": "en", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 109886, "n_unique_entities": 120, "n_entity_mentions": 2315, "sigma": 274.715, "target_scenes": 36, "detected_scene_boundaries": [2970.2076923076925, 5478.371153846154, 7465.993376068376, 8819.122222222222, 10708.901587301589, 13602.739087301587, 15972.234375, 17347.07068452381, 20168.06380952381, 23125.33651162791, 26155.49196617336, 29441.682296650717, 31170.053508771933, 32617.171739130434, 35780.59975331483, 39019.52649903289, 41062.04712430427, 43576.62530612245, 45990.34148148148, 48347.94115890084, 52145.48695014663, 55404.7337944664, 56866.564855072465, 58597.60277777778, 61105.101587301586, 63482.87601078167, 64988.55590496157, 66849.16861598441, 69384.94110275689, 71870.60022148394, 74588.30368468742, 76754.67348084015, 79032.6280262947, 81454.37882279011, 83521.0224014337, 86567.66666666666, 89474.32828282828, 93238.20889748549, 97508.97188449849, 99977.03571428571, 103155.87121212122, 106423.82895860009], "n_scenes": 43, "top_entities": [{"label": "lady", "count": 292, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "donald", "count": 140, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "chick", "count": 135, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "sequin", "count": 109, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "connie", "count": 100, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "myrtella", "count": 95, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "gooch", "count": 73, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "gerald", "count": 68, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "noah", "count": 67, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "don", "count": 56, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "queerington", "count": 48, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "bertie", "count": 44, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "jimpson", "count": 43, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "phineas", "count": 41, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "margery", "count": 40, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "dillingham", "count": 38, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "thornwood", "count": 38, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "uncle jimpson", "count": 37, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "sheeley", "count": 37, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "decker", "count": 35, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "flathers", "count": 35, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "hattie", "count": 35, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "maria", "count": 31, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "morley", "count": 26, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "hill", "count": 24, "type": "PERSON"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 80421.08804402202, "activity": 0.04167959143577614}, {"token": 76573.18909454728, "activity": 0.038760653073084676}, {"token": 90480.59529764883, "activity": 0.03858317899794346}, {"token": 46834.4272136068, "activity": 0.03670224252042037}, {"token": 77892.46873436718, "activity": 0.03643438640041498}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 43, "edges": 721, "scene_entity_counts": [21, 14, 13, 13, 18, 22, 9, 9, 19, 18, 29, 21, 14, 17, 28, 21, 12, 20, 14, 16, 24, 24, 11, 17, 20, 18, 20, 11, 12, 20, 21, 26, 25, 26, 21, 29, 16, 24, 27, 22, 26, 24, 29]}, "elapsed_s": 9.75}
{"slug": "A_Room_with_a_View_E_M_Forster", "title": "A Room with a View E M Forster", "language": "en", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 91553, "n_unique_entities": 100, "n_entity_mentions": 2302, "sigma": 228.8825, "target_scenes": 30, "detected_scene_boundaries": [3103.3176914778855, 9759.342324601575, 17917.56562557245, 22829.758164165934, 25655.88811188811, 28243.484432234432, 31043.966062544423, 35022.3296881927, 40420.58633180391, 45897.19500469043, 49991.7536268556, 52502.597994987475, 54453.03571428571, 57671.97280701754, 61055.97697368421, 64106.05892857142, 67927.98681318681, 73606.26435216701, 79563.13316295392, 82724.02199608958, 85080.2157286152, 87522.23965632298], "n_scenes": 23, "top_entities": [{"label": "lucy", "count": 461, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "beebe", "count": 203, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "bartlett", "count": 198, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "freddy", "count": 125, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "honeychurch", "count": 111, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "emerson", "count": 98, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "charlotte", "count": 89, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "george", "count": 86, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "eager", "count": 56, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "italy", "count": 54, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "florence", "count": 43, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "lavish", "count": 40, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "vyse", "count": 40, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "windy corner", "count": 32, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "alans", "count": 31, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "emersons", "count": 30, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "minnie", "count": 27, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "greece", "count": 27, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "london", "count": 26, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "rome", "count": 25, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "italian", "count": 21, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "george emerson", "count": 19, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "harry", "count": 19, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "santa croce", "count": 17, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "alan", "count": 17, "type": "PERSON"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 13648.07203601801, "activity": 0.04701793674810586}, {"token": 24914.601300650327, "activity": 0.046080740135466244}, {"token": 366.3911955977989, "activity": 0.04542421006829246}, {"token": 81522.04102051025, "activity": 0.04443216747328281}, {"token": 50561.98499249625, "activity": 0.04316987213539131}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 23, "edges": 498, "scene_entity_counts": [27, 35, 38, 28, 32, 20, 13, 17, 29, 28, 30, 28, 15, 18, 26, 28, 35, 27, 33, 27, 23, 16, 25]}, "elapsed_s": 8.11}
{"slug": "A_Study_in_Scarlet_Arthur_Conan_Doyle", "status": "skipped", "elapsed_s": 0.0}
{"slug": "A_farewell_to_arms_Ernest_Hemingway", "title": "A farewell to arms Ernest Hemingway", "language": "en", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 123201, "n_unique_entities": 106, "n_entity_mentions": 1473, "sigma": 308.0025, "target_scenes": 41, "detected_scene_boundaries": [1793.3148148148148, 5160.652937420178, 9200.36986863711, 12334.917366946778, 15741.54723707665, 19596.136762360446, 22770.239035087718, 25334.916666666664, 27348.777985074626, 29781.55515898767, 31981.78550724638, 34664.21228070175, 38212.06170598911, 41618.739901477835, 45712.80714285714, 50516.24565217391, 54579.49565217391, 56970.45, 58667.842307692306, 60297.86730769231, 62270.9875, 64882.7125, 68401.51764705882, 71900.79820261439, 74873.84093291406, 77331.97072218609, 79737.03761755486, 83917.72727272726, 87670.88888888889, 89922.98371647511, 93220.2548275862, 96508.39076923077, 98479.83603238866, 99981.716374269, 101817.0379403794, 103694.21254355401, 106133.73883928571, 109136.40767045454, 111697.14204545454, 114198.9875, 116420.42000000001, 118780.58153846154, 121230.52820512821], "n_scenes": 44, "top_entities": [{"label": "catherine", "count": 268, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "rinaldi", "count": 72, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "tenente", "count": 68, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "piani", "count": 59, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "italian", "count": 57, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "bonello", "count": 48, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "ferguson", "count": 37, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "american", "count": 35, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "austrians", "count": 34, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "aymo", "count": 32, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "milan", "count": 30, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "italians", "count": 30, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "barkley", "count": 29, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "germans", "count": 23, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "ettore", "count": 21, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "montreux", "count": 21, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "british", "count": 19, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "austrian", "count": 18, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "udine", "count": 17, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "manera", "count": 16, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "rome", "count": 15, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "italy", "count": 15, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "van campen", "count": 15, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "fergy", "count": 15, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "switzerland", "count": 14, "type": "GPE"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 28165.28264132066, "activity": 0.05176706726397296}, {"token": 91090.34517258628, "activity": 0.04475077225991214}, {"token": 6964.282141070535, "activity": 0.03798377455601635}, {"token": 43634.61730865433, "activity": 0.037051817561076276}, {"token": 70505.6528264132, "activity": 0.035970370065507434}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 44, "edges": 355, "scene_entity_counts": [7, 13, 19, 14, 24, 11, 12, 8, 6, 22, 10, 14, 9, 13, 29, 25, 7, 5, 3, 13, 6, 8, 14, 17, 10, 8, 11, 15, 7, 12, 13, 9, 5, 5, 3, 9, 9, 9, 7, 8, 2, 4, 3, 3]}, "elapsed_s": 10.88}
{"slug": "A_pair_of_blue_eyes_Thomas_Hardy", "title": "A pair of blue eyes Thomas Hardy", "language": "en", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 173950, "n_unique_entities": 89, "n_entity_mentions": 2723, "sigma": 434.875, "target_scenes": 57, "detected_scene_boundaries": [5626.5, 8446.767025089604, 11646.552310374891, 13656.27027027027, 15161.220027720028, 17667.009032634032, 20098.557806324112, 22112.525879917186, 25876.397619047617, 29080.48888888889, 30509.24074074074, 33079.665284687675, 36890.54070556309, 39694.41019955654, 41641.48292682927, 44174.60769230769, 48053.20965309201, 51243.41547429783, 53791.84163851351, 56296.78125, 58770.91145833333, 62430.21875, 65217.922181372545, 66854.69402277039, 68726.04169202677, 71464.59514824799, 74295.31648351648, 76699.76525198939, 79452.33883058472, 83147.55434782608, 86205.36702127659, 88346.76218256692, 90311.63266129032, 92217.409375, 94731.54092261905, 98964.9962406015, 102656.44498959262, 105296.3003547497, 108104.51304594442, 109756.90048780487, 111416.14777777778, 114117.5611111111, 117119.95, 119324.38145539907, 121867.22949461474, 124517.58137254902, 126811.98687943263, 129744.82762017337, 132380.17464878672, 134713.1054766734, 137883.0644257703, 140455.1684981685, 142086.6923076923, 145376.55, 148721.74318181816, 150581.59858722356, 152178.24324324325, 153504.76208026207, 155952.61779081135, 159198.9097646033, 162053.98605748604, 165276.05555555556, 168361.66806722688, 170641.74084350723], "n_scenes": 65, "top_entities": [{"label": "knight", "count": 596, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "elfride", "count": 447, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "stephen", "count": 421, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "swancourt", "count": 237, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "smith", "count": 116, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "london", "count": 69, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "stephen’s", "count": 65, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "luxellian", "count": 62, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "endelstow", "count": 38, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "jethway", "count": 37, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "stephen smith", "count": 36, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "harry", "count": 35, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "elfie", "count": 34, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "john", "count": 31, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "st. launce’s", "count": 27, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "castle boterel", "count": 25, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "john smith", "count": 23, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "england", "count": 19, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "plymouth", "count": 19, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "worm", "count": 18, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "william worm", "count": 15, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "martin", "count": 15, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "hewby", "count": 14, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "martin cannister", "count": 12, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "india", "count": 12, "type": "GPE"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 118170.45622811405, "activity": 0.03244341117387833}, {"token": 120519.94247123561, "activity": 0.03129633243202966}, {"token": 35155.27563781891, "activity": 0.0306040676323361}, {"token": 171773.54977488745, "activity": 0.029528409993880834}, {"token": 161679.4607303652, "activity": 0.02920869104248971}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 65, "edges": 646, "scene_entity_counts": [22, 10, 10, 9, 9, 10, 11, 13, 9, 8, 4, 10, 21, 14, 7, 6, 17, 14, 12, 9, 12, 14, 10, 11, 6, 10, 7, 6, 6, 13, 12, 13, 8, 13, 6, 4, 16, 19, 14, 12, 13, 14, 17, 14, 13, 9, 7, 12, 10, 6, 9, 11, 6, 11, 11, 8, 8, 5, 10, 21, 15, 14, 21, 12, 21]}, "elapsed_s": 15.52}
{"slug": "Around_the_World_in_Eighty_Days_Jules_Verne", "title": "Around the World in Eighty Days Jules Verne", "language": "en", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 84163, "n_unique_entities": 141, "n_entity_mentions": 2176, "sigma": 210.4075, "target_scenes": 28, "detected_scene_boundaries": [3564.75702247191, 7201.770082173402, 10776.74655026753, 13178.332628497072, 15138.609852216749, 17168.68571428571, 18537.386206896554, 19922.240316485593, 22385.627323874753, 24943.848214285714, 26943.409722222223, 29615.23399758454, 32334.211775362317, 35588.9509057971, 39847.3185427834, 43117.974581430746, 45672.86168582375, 48660.28898050975, 51457.10262148338, 53831.67703619909, 55947.3141025641, 58690.595221445226, 61549.39727272728, 64301.51137931035, 67010.24137931035, 69936.15217391304, 72637.20078502415, 75496.73170970267, 78785.43661971831, 80930.0352112676], "n_scenes": 31, "top_entities": [{"label": "fogg", "count": 512, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "aouda", "count": 135, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "phileas fogg", "count": 88, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "london", "count": 64, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "hong kong", "count": 62, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "bombay", "count": 60, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "francis", "count": 41, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "yokohama", "count": 40, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "india", "count": 35, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "indian", "count": 31, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "parsee", "count": 31, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "american", "count": 30, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "liverpool", "count": 28, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "new york", "count": 28, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "san francisco", "count": 28, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "fix", "count": 25, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "suez", "count": 25, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "indians", "count": 24, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "omaha", "count": 24, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "japanese", "count": 22, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "the reform club", "count": 21, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "england", "count": 21, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "english", "count": 19, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "frenchman", "count": 19, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "stuart", "count": 18, "type": "PERSON"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 5725.878939469735, "activity": 0.06081936879331872}, {"token": 57300.89144572286, "activity": 0.05853296502026958}, {"token": 37512.92746373187, "activity": 0.049796228539760186}, {"token": 42270.45922961481, "activity": 0.0480085686002043}, {"token": 81972.69334667335, "activity": 0.047892150114173526}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 31, "edges": 538, "scene_entity_counts": [21, 33, 32, 22, 19, 21, 17, 12, 18, 17, 8, 27, 24, 31, 29, 24, 16, 21, 23, 28, 27, 34, 23, 22, 23, 11, 19, 22, 17, 15, 23]}, "elapsed_s": 7.8}
{"slug": "As_You_Like_It_William_Shakespeare", "title": "As You Like It William Shakespeare", "language": "en", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 32581, "n_unique_entities": 44, "n_entity_mentions": 662, "sigma": 81.4525, "target_scenes": 10, "detected_scene_boundaries": [4828.719851258581, 9790.44668784029, 14859.07879310345, 19383.813514851485, 24582.92258892556], "n_scenes": 6, "top_entities": [{"label": "orlando", "count": 167, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "jaques", "count": 71, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "phoebe", "count": 48, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "oliver", "count": 44, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "thou", "count": 37, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "audrey", "count": 26, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "adam", "count": 23, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "charles", "count": 22, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "celia", "count": 18, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "silvius", "count": 18, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "william", "count": 16, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "nay", "count": 15, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "le beau", "count": 14, "type": "FAC"}, {"label": "exit", "count": 11, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "duke", "count": 10, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "marry", "count": 8, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "aliena", "count": 8, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "rowland", "count": 7, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "shall", "count": 6, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "rosalind", "count": 6, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "hose", "count": 6, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "the forest of arden", "count": 5, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "amiens", "count": 5, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "oliver’s", "count": 4, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "oliver martext", "count": 4, "type": "PERSON"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 814.9074537268634, "activity": 0.07428569671686759}, {"token": 16705.6028014007, "activity": 0.06680509220268216}, {"token": 27087.523761880937, "activity": 0.060926199269785396}, {"token": 29907.103551775886, "activity": 0.056094214968018766}, {"token": 1613.5167583791895, "activity": 0.056031404221248055}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 6, "edges": 86, "scene_entity_counts": [26, 25, 18, 18, 19, 24]}, "elapsed_s": 3.17}
{"slug": "Aus_dem_Leben_eines_Taugenichts_Novelle_Joseph_Eichendorff", "title": "Aus dem Leben eines Taugenichts Novelle Joseph Eichendorff", "language": "de", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 39626, "n_unique_entities": 64, "n_entity_mentions": 372, "sigma": 99.065, "target_scenes": 13, "detected_scene_boundaries": [8922.7781124498, 14394.25469483568, 20231.1423759951, 27487.109035326088, 34128.015955105635], "n_scenes": 6, "top_entities": [{"label": "italien", "count": 21, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "andern", "count": 17, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "leonhard", "count": 17, "type": "PER"}, {"label": "mir", "count": 12, "type": "MISC"}, {"label": "bergen", "count": 12, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "rom", "count": 12, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "damen", "count": 10, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "stadt", "count": 10, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "hause", "count": 10, "type": "PER"}, {"label": "donau", "count": 10, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "guido", "count": 10, "type": "PER"}, {"label": "mond", "count": 9, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "erde", "count": 9, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "zeit", "count": 8, "type": "MISC"}, {"label": "mirs", "count": 8, "type": "PER"}, {"label": "wand", "count": 7, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "lerchen", "count": 7, "type": "MISC"}, {"label": "ach", "count": 7, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "kerl", "count": 6, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "deutschland", "count": 6, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "magd", "count": 6, "type": "MISC"}, {"label": "wien", "count": 5, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "kutscher", "count": 5, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "fenster", "count": 5, "type": "PER"}, {"label": "kirche", "count": 5, "type": "ORG"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 23033.641820910456, "activity": 0.03419445368690321}, {"token": 3171.5857928964483, "activity": 0.02705162442764597}, {"token": 39387.13106553277, "activity": 0.025854868394346548}, {"token": 25868.246623311654, "activity": 0.025103078707747153}, {"token": 38059.02951475738, "activity": 0.024234972004187214}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 6, "edges": 117, "scene_entity_counts": [40, 24, 26, 33, 31, 27]}, "elapsed_s": 4.1}
{"slug": "Autobiography_of_Benjamin_Franklin_Benjamin_Franklin", "title": "Autobiography of Benjamin Franklin Benjamin Franklin", "language": "en", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 98313, "n_unique_entities": 156, "n_entity_mentions": 1348, "sigma": 245.7825, "target_scenes": 32, "detected_scene_boundaries": [2946.8977554179564, 4879.557843137255, 7808.760416666666, 11183.431985294119, 13773.82037815126, 16681.223668280873, 21580.31049094097, 25667.024847870183, 28143.611287758344, 30474.3566249176, 33712.066604127576, 37090.212158808936, 39027.55677419355, 40783.23777777777, 43221.11111111111, 45354.90476190476, 48085.553571428565, 51446.675691244236, 54509.64809384164, 56889.3354978355, 58244.250517598346, 59611.353436185134, 61439.93699596774, 63132.453125, 64985.96666666667, 67712.18988095238, 69834.17321428572, 71692.23125, 73959.24553571429, 76180.39906832298, 79238.57203751066, 82407.4705882353, 85690.72522522524, 88938.43633633634, 91752.93250414594, 94613.510010921, 96613.26901004303], "n_scenes": 38, "top_entities": [{"label": "franklin", "count": 93, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "philadelphia", "count": 71, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "england", "count": 50, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "assembly", "count": 49, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "london", "count": 48, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "boston", "count": 41, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "keimer", "count": 36, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "new york", "count": 34, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "pennsylvania", "count": 31, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "thro", "count": 31, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "america", "count": 29, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "house", "count": 27, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "french", "count": 22, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "ralph", "count": 20, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "american", "count": 19, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "france", "count": 16, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "richard", "count": 16, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "bradford", "count": 16, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "indians", "count": 15, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "paris", "count": 14, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "new england", "count": 13, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "braddock", "count": 12, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "junto", "count": 12, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "time", "count": 12, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "us'd", "count": 11, "type": "ORG"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 3836.0860430215107, "activity": 0.04728288680042213}, {"token": 93541.48274137068, "activity": 0.043411543389963524}, {"token": 1721.320660330165, "activity": 0.042949928736360075}, {"token": 3000.016008004002, "activity": 0.04122341172398646}, {"token": 18442.72136068034, "activity": 0.03278714474812957}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 38, "edges": 496, "scene_entity_counts": [27, 23, 16, 13, 15, 16, 29, 26, 9, 19, 23, 16, 14, 12, 6, 4, 9, 14, 21, 12, 5, 12, 13, 18, 8, 9, 25, 21, 11, 24, 13, 27, 23, 21, 22, 34, 24, 18]}, "elapsed_s": 8.93}
{"slug": "Autobiography_of_a_Yogi_Paramahansa_Yogananda", "title": "Autobiography of a Yogi Paramahansa Yogananda", "language": "en", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 205936, "n_unique_entities": 327, "n_entity_mentions": 4051, "sigma": 514.84, "target_scenes": 60, "detected_scene_boundaries": [2740.05873015873, 5293.025606469003, 8045.1557651991625, 11600.101587301588, 15493.211688311689, 19633.610795454544, 24877.59375, 30603.5375, 35212.51666666666, 39092.630952380954, 42143.8354978355, 46076.29166666667, 49673.85412801484, 52271.020882771714, 54787.92544459645, 57473.049019607846, 61270.46078431372, 64140.259259259255, 66787.31878306878, 70456.15327380953, 73670.38444767441, 77049.57641196014, 80700.63030888031, 83956.3633445946, 87573.8264423077, 90346.61769230769, 92929.32612903226, 96523.60483870967, 99662.7156938044, 103058.58253968254, 106725.22529239766, 109512.23242340927, 113421.28877352369, 118344.72423510466, 121921.3639015728, 124895.32075342466, 127375.65151162792, 130378.74963662791, 134544.6725127551, 137595.2756377551, 139868.95975877193, 142641.14239766082, 145156.56436058698, 147390.46362959285, 149370.30698906357, 151786.74308859458, 155181.39893275042, 158680.46585179528, 162114.29060175794, 165028.51174412793, 167494.17481884058, 171011.91898148146, 177082.55886243386, 182872.45238095237, 185849.78, 189010.68588235293, 192629.61884531588, 194950.71296296298, 198469.011627907, 202539.44344608882], "n_scenes": 61, "top_entities": [{"label": "india", "count": 201, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "lahiri mahasaya", "count": 186, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "sri yukteswar", "count": 176, "type": "FAC"}, {"label": "babaji", "count": 124, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "hindu", "count": 72, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "indian", "count": 71, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "america", "count": 67, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "benares", "count": 65, "type": "FAC"}, {"label": "sri yukteswar’s", "count": 60, "type": "FAC"}, {"label": "gandhi", "count": 58, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "sanskrit", "count": 53, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "ranchi", "count": 52, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "ananta", "count": 49, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "chapter", "count": 48, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "wright", "count": 47, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "kriya", "count": 46, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "bengali", "count": 43, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "west", "count": 39, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "spirit", "count": 37, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "therese", "count": 36, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "serampore", "count": 34, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "lahiri mahasaya’s", "count": 33, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "american", "count": 32, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "jesus", "count": 32, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "puri", "count": 31, "type": "GPE"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 927.1710855427714, "activity": 0.04463760940787861}, {"token": 173484.012006003, "activity": 0.04306096992563334}, {"token": 136397.16858429214, "activity": 0.03967177915477888}, {"token": 153498.32416208103, "activity": 0.0378345873111978}, {"token": 146493.03151575787, "activity": 0.03757961650418079}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 61, "edges": 1434, "scene_entity_counts": [50, 17, 26, 24, 33, 38, 24, 31, 30, 21, 32, 34, 27, 21, 8, 19, 29, 13, 16, 25, 23, 24, 27, 23, 28, 24, 20, 35, 35, 29, 33, 33, 30, 24, 17, 24, 43, 32, 19, 30, 27, 26, 27, 40, 21, 30, 41, 40, 44, 24, 31, 43, 57, 17, 33, 23, 30, 17, 26, 49, 44]}, "elapsed_s": 20.02}
{"slug": "Bidwells_Travels_from_Wall_Street_to_London_Prison_Fifteen_Years_in_Solitude_Austin_Bidwell", "title": "Bidwells Travels from Wall Street to London Prison Fifteen Years in Solitude Austin Bidwell", "language": "en", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 169988, "n_unique_entities": 259, "n_entity_mentions": 2771, "sigma": 424.97, "target_scenes": 56, "detected_scene_boundaries": [6305.25153643547, 12291.039915966387, 15974.41917293233, 20351.954887218046, 25735.164682539682, 29340.23611111111, 33576.78676470588, 37958.092320261436, 40824.774305555555, 43228.28125, 45661.66032608696, 48069.29328063241, 50368.94545454545, 53176.19607843137, 55456.01129582268, 57833.762025901946, 59920.140686061655, 61745.14700255102, 64368.534007352944, 67637.16578801331, 70355.61268343816, 73204.35233918129, 76907.49763832659, 81602.05465587045, 87912.81636155606, 92580.71156832298, 94693.98133116882, 97440.71212121213, 100660.16886608016, 103942.56129032258, 109382.72236842106, 114741.98563372718, 118189.82149315422, 121332.5644778481, 125302.95386904762, 128839.73992673992, 131896.2173076923, 135536.75833333333, 139120.54583333334, 141976.88392857142, 143596.85714285716, 145327.7857142857, 147562.36666666667, 150103.04234234235, 152816.9501854796, 155726.96749226004, 158409.68161881977, 162680.42863636365, 167310.24357142858], "n_scenes": 50, "top_entities": [{"label": "london", "count": 174, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "mac", "count": 142, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "new york", "count": 81, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "paris", "count": 71, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "england", "count": 63, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "george", "count": 55, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "american", "count": 54, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "america", "count": 53, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "james", "count": 47, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "irving", "count": 46, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "the bank of england", "count": 46, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "havana", "count": 44, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "nunn", "count": 43, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "noyes", "count": 42, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "europe", "count": 40, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "brea", "count": 39, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "spanish", "count": 35, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "cuba", "count": 33, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "french", "count": 31, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "countess", "count": 29, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "france", "count": 29, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "rio", "count": 27, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "madrid", "count": 26, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "ireland", "count": 24, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "f. a. warren", "count": 23, "type": "PERSON"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 84440.76588294147, "activity": 0.04922176082765815}, {"token": 119560.64132066033, "activity": 0.041199219671835034}, {"token": 23640.013006503254, "activity": 0.03831266102643525}, {"token": 133676.6203101551, "activity": 0.03777410217839974}, {"token": 36650.52376188094, "activity": 0.0376500298458446}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 50, "edges": 853, "scene_entity_counts": [65, 25, 26, 16, 42, 15, 26, 23, 17, 23, 18, 18, 24, 18, 27, 16, 16, 14, 11, 32, 20, 33, 34, 26, 51, 18, 25, 21, 36, 18, 27, 51, 27, 38, 16, 10, 8, 36, 18, 5, 1, 7, 4, 7, 16, 18, 20, 21, 14, 14]}, "elapsed_s": 14.91}
{"slug": "Blow_The_Man_Down_A_Romance_Of_The_Coast_Holman_Day", "title": "Blow The Man Down A Romance Of The Coast Holman Day", "language": "en", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 188927, "n_unique_entities": 106, "n_entity_mentions": 2740, "sigma": 472.3175, "target_scenes": 60, "detected_scene_boundaries": [3953.941598360656, 6551.854098360656, 9540.88813559322, 13708.714061519146, 17893.835016835015, 20875.920454545456, 23828.787959381043, 26761.276595744683, 29463.0, 32199.365384615383, 34289.653846153844, 35716.0298408488, 37302.38268365817, 39821.00895140665, 42930.653361344535, 46471.73469387755, 49495.914888682746, 51834.28298226164, 55931.64399624766, 59684.91025641025, 62051.339147286824, 64812.80268895349, 68101.82347074468, 70724.33909574468, 72841.21366279069, 74875.59560723514, 76569.92118863048, 79152.92118863048, 81475.95555555556, 82922.24366925065, 84982.66827242525, 87273.8880952381, 90118.22657450076, 94248.70102281668, 98172.62195121951, 103046.65256875973, 107826.87636572742, 110888.83783783784, 113588.05225225225, 116078.8462962963, 118161.86982570807, 120408.40104879161, 124101.3367786391, 127277.6425925926, 129227.86707317072, 132060.2409862142, 135140.8428319624, 138304.09538950716, 141944.66583229037, 145154.5991177997, 148098.6757938334, 151055.88655055634, 154032.0005128205, 157298.54111111112, 160444.3304988662, 162558.16383219953, 164517.8803418803, 168059.48852901484, 172084.38596491228, 174592.76515151514, 176949.5328820116, 180316.12975235438, 183008.27021394833, 185059.39331113803], "n_scenes": 65, "top_entities": [{"label": "mayo", "count": 891, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "fogg", "count": 234, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "marston", "count": 167, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "bradish", "count": 112, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "captain candage", "count": 104, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "downs", "count": 76, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "wass", "count": 69, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "olenia", "count": 43, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "montana", "count": 42, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "julius marston", "count": 41, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "speed", "count": 39, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "conomo", "count": 37, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "burkett", "count": 37, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "rowley", "count": 32, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "maquoit", "count": 31, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "new york", "count": 29, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "alma marston", "count": 27, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "boyd", "count": 26, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "boyne", "count": 26, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "razee", "count": 25, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "ethel", "count": 23, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "may", "count": 23, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "alma", "count": 22, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "nequasset", "count": 21, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "dolph", "count": 20, "type": "GPE"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 166149.02851425714, "activity": 0.03301616444829124}, {"token": 11246.72036018009, "activity": 0.027011053907128355}, {"token": 181837.7308654327, "activity": 0.026541375763218144}, {"token": 173426.31815907953, "activity": 0.025909498860739393}, {"token": 184484.0180090045, "activity": 0.025326964873065124}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 65, "edges": 628, "scene_entity_counts": [15, 13, 11, 18, 10, 7, 18, 14, 7, 8, 5, 7, 7, 10, 10, 10, 11, 12, 16, 12, 6, 9, 6, 13, 14, 9, 7, 12, 11, 8, 8, 12, 19, 14, 11, 11, 14, 16, 7, 5, 8, 8, 12, 7, 4, 6, 8, 8, 9, 16, 20, 16, 12, 6, 12, 10, 10, 17, 18, 12, 12, 23, 18, 6, 23]}, "elapsed_s": 15.55}
{"slug": "Camille_La_Dame_aux_Camilias_Alexandre_Dumas", "title": "Camille La Dame aux Camilias Alexandre Dumas", "language": "en", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 86283, "n_unique_entities": 41, "n_entity_mentions": 911, "sigma": 215.7075, "target_scenes": 28, "detected_scene_boundaries": [3296.7438423645317, 4915.632413793103, 6999.525217391304, 9971.27950310559, 13092.3489010989, 15375.174615384614, 19282.48318181818, 23199.23106060606, 24608.67850378788, 27019.015625, 30062.103260869568, 32040.500988142296, 33493.12272727273, 36081.85, 39536.315217391304, 42821.50070126227, 45207.659621802, 47665.824137931035, 50735.369230769225, 53259.22511312217, 55955.32767722473, 59200.2317948718, 62424.09809523809, 65170.079558652724, 67423.32675753228, 69401.756127451, 72291.20138888889, 76175.38510101009, 78820.55454545454, 80206.76000000001, 83246.29461538463], "n_scenes": 32, "top_entities": [{"label": "marguerite", "count": 376, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "paris", "count": 85, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "armand", "count": 80, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "prudence", "count": 59, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "gaston", "count": 34, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "mme", "count": 30, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "nanine", "count": 21, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "duvernoy", "count": 20, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "mlle", "count": 19, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "bougival", "count": 15, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "joseph", "count": 12, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "marguerite gautier", "count": 10, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "olympe", "count": 10, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "bagnères", "count": 9, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "manon", "count": 9, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "the champs-elysées", "count": 8, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "julie duprat", "count": 8, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "the rue d’antin", "count": 8, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "m. de g.", "count": 8, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "manon lescaut", "count": 7, "type": "FAC"}, {"label": "m. duval", "count": 6, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "gautier’s", "count": 5, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "the opera comique", "count": 5, "type": "FAC"}, {"label": "champs-elysées", "count": 5, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "vaudeville", "count": 5, "type": "GPE"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 85764.04902451225, "activity": 0.026069350156860363}, {"token": 56974.60730365182, "activity": 0.02588472791008239}, {"token": 22487.704852426214, "activity": 0.024948797517488543}, {"token": 68671.6668334167, "activity": 0.02491831534032818}, {"token": 52744.67433716858, "activity": 0.024669441989827182}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 32, "edges": 234, "scene_entity_counts": [5, 6, 8, 10, 6, 8, 10, 13, 9, 4, 6, 5, 6, 6, 8, 9, 13, 6, 6, 10, 8, 12, 10, 7, 9, 13, 8, 15, 8, 5, 13, 13]}, "elapsed_s": 7.41}
{"slug": "Carmen_Prosper_Mérimée", "title": "Carmen Prosper Mérimée", "language": "en", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 31672, "n_unique_entities": 46, "n_entity_mentions": 337, "sigma": 79.18, "target_scenes": 10, "detected_scene_boundaries": [7016.120740740741, 11935.211670973298, 15308.854263565892, 19831.470833333333, 26141.776524390243], "n_scenes": 6, "top_entities": [{"label": "carmen", "count": 28, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "spanish", "count": 19, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "el dancaire", "count": 18, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "garcia", "count": 18, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "seville", "count": 17, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "cordova", "count": 16, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "basque", "count": 16, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "spain", "count": 12, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "don jose", "count": 12, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "antonio", "count": 11, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "gibraltar", "count": 11, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "romany", "count": 10, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "calle del candilejo", "count": 8, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "andalusia", "count": 7, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "andalusian", "count": 7, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "dorotea", "count": 7, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "lucas", "count": 7, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "jose-maria", "count": 6, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "german", "count": 6, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "montilla", "count": 5, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "navarre", "count": 5, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "navarrese", "count": 5, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "i.", "count": 5, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "english", "count": 5, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "don pedro", "count": 5, "type": "PERSON"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 31179.853926963482, "activity": 0.0338532817252356}, {"token": 23971.09704852426, "activity": 0.033669645687093526}, {"token": 21515.366683341672, "activity": 0.03308481637535356}, {"token": 21087.594297148575, "activity": 0.030448125137242644}, {"token": 31005.57628814407, "activity": 0.03039722363547472}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 6, "edges": 68, "scene_entity_counts": [20, 22, 13, 17, 26, 16]}, "elapsed_s": 2.85}
{"slug": "Catriona_Robert_Louis_Stevenson", "title": "Catriona Robert Louis Stevenson", "language": "en", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 131850, "n_unique_entities": 135, "n_entity_mentions": 1863, "sigma": 329.625, "target_scenes": 43, "detected_scene_boundaries": [2570.7884615384614, 5324.451923076923, 7792.328846153846, 10242.687267904508, 12666.310344827587, 15287.351351351352, 17604.92277992278, 19029.680124223603, 20896.829625884733, 23878.470930232557, 27099.09210526316, 29379.002105263156, 32437.447037037036, 35172.55118798043, 38555.40545529123, 42895.54606625259, 45494.84378629501, 47810.63694105692, 49789.5393800813, 52655.641463414635, 55935.62222222222, 57645.03472222222, 59298.9993852459, 61524.276885245905, 63790.55818181818, 66771.62587412588, 70302.91483516485, 73438.29714285715, 76103.29714285715, 78722.26623376623, 81518.26203208556, 83525.15939278937, 85850.17487266554, 88884.82675438597, 91352.50961538462, 94303.14338731444, 98156.37781954888, 101940.55238095239, 105292.42183908046, 107854.49608150471, 110847.31233766234, 113662.05142857143, 115451.155, 117467.62045454545, 119950.98181818181, 122880.43636363637, 126206.8309859155, 129142.9877023334], "n_scenes": 49, "top_entities": [{"label": "alan", "count": 202, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "i.", "count": 188, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "catriona", "count": 143, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "james more", "count": 83, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "james", "count": 74, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "balfour", "count": 69, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "david", "count": 65, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "stewart", "count": 56, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "andie", "count": 52, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "drummond", "count": 32, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "neil", "count": 30, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "grant", "count": 28, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "scotland", "count": 27, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "bass", "count": 26, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "highland", "count": 23, "type": "FAC"}, {"label": "simon", "count": 22, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "david balfour", "count": 21, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "french", "count": 21, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "leyden", "count": 21, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "i. “", "count": 20, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "tam", "count": 18, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "campbell", "count": 17, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "edinburgh", "count": 17, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "sandie", "count": 14, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "appin", "count": 13, "type": "ORG"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 8904.259629814907, "activity": 0.038302674839961734}, {"token": 128221.33866933468, "activity": 0.03385508523061651}, {"token": 130463.89294647325, "activity": 0.030821713036522667}, {"token": 60944.710355177594, "activity": 0.029024034367017497}, {"token": 62329.81740870436, "activity": 0.027758042552422615}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 49, "edges": 668, "scene_entity_counts": [21, 23, 17, 21, 15, 9, 13, 10, 12, 19, 21, 11, 15, 28, 27, 26, 21, 15, 11, 17, 18, 13, 11, 12, 21, 29, 21, 22, 18, 15, 13, 17, 19, 16, 14, 19, 23, 14, 7, 13, 6, 16, 5, 6, 8, 17, 15, 17, 26]}, "elapsed_s": 11.47}
{"slug": "Complete_Short_Works_of_George_Meredith_George_Meredith", "title": "Complete Short Works of George Meredith George Meredith", "language": "en", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 220623, "n_unique_entities": 301, "n_entity_mentions": 4416, "sigma": 551.5575, "target_scenes": 60, "detected_scene_boundaries": [4844.950830419581, 8128.739583333333, 9907.676587301587, 12394.615312791782, 16737.099186483105, 21153.680941218896, 24374.189597873046, 27030.97268907563, 29924.227813852813, 35813.59565592635, 42243.933080168776, 47440.701060606065, 51941.89262523191, 55276.85465405675, 58451.53163109756, 60845.13778409091, 63189.00901253919, 65965.522833178, 68459.14639639639, 71190.56531531531, 75468.22900579151, 79593.5656512605, 83216.97904411764, 87268.58303571428, 91004.0801948052, 94309.8502840909, 97471.15667229731, 100733.64864864865, 105727.07178145889, 110956.02346041056, 114667.20303030303, 118851.49375, 122986.34375, 127737.96022727274, 132266.62914619164, 136026.93504795118, 139872.94570649706, 142976.37463240983, 146267.41727716726, 150131.6977124183, 153249.55307640298, 155317.88314176246, 157762.7380952381, 162125.51806599833, 168821.49342105264, 174497.93730650155, 178655.79256965942, 183184.17085020244, 187172.72362637363, 190595.9969685487, 193508.5544912729, 195582.81026997694, 199436.28014652015, 205150.84064516128, 210245.51397849462, 214936.21666666667], "n_scenes": 57, "top_entities": [{"label": "tinman", "count": 198, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "margarita", "count": 165, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "farina", "count": 163, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "chloe", "count": 159, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "camper", "count": 129, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "crickledon", "count": 105, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "van diemen", "count": 103, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "beamish", "count": 97, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "italian", "count": 88, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "pollingray", "count": 86, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "gottlieb", "count": 72, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "fellingham", "count": 71, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "elizabeth", "count": 70, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "werner", "count": 65, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "guy", "count": 61, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "cologne", "count": 60, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "herbert", "count": 56, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "england", "count": 54, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "austrian", "count": 54, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "comic", "count": 51, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "comedy", "count": 51, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "french", "count": 49, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "kaiser", "count": 48, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "aunt lisbeth", "count": 47, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "austrians", "count": 45, "type": "NORP"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 181000.54027013507, "activity": 0.05654356251258367}, {"token": 44919.036518259134, "activity": 0.051241415919224126}, {"token": 2869.52076038019, "activity": 0.04806663710311031}, {"token": 185635.91995998, "activity": 0.04599990262596865}, {"token": 144469.33366683344, "activity": 0.03873360263214254}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 57, "edges": 885, "scene_entity_counts": [41, 27, 11, 16, 14, 27, 13, 18, 17, 33, 26, 48, 15, 6, 10, 6, 18, 13, 9, 7, 18, 12, 10, 22, 13, 10, 7, 8, 18, 32, 24, 22, 25, 22, 26, 26, 28, 19, 22, 6, 9, 11, 10, 12, 30, 16, 30, 51, 46, 34, 16, 26, 39, 28, 36, 20, 27]}, "elapsed_s": 18.54}
{"slug": "Cranford_Elizabeth_Cleghorn_Gaskell", "title": "Cranford Elizabeth Cleghorn Gaskell", "language": "en", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 92528, "n_unique_entities": 93, "n_entity_mentions": 1901, "sigma": 231.32, "target_scenes": 30, "detected_scene_boundaries": [3040.5834748160723, 6647.380542264753, 8900.28712121212, 10924.221078431372, 14124.834099264706, 17463.315557065216, 20438.091226708075, 24399.466720779223, 27881.508912655972, 30720.039215686273, 34402.43827160494, 37066.17677735207, 39257.44785534062, 42484.5218495935, 45431.38988095238, 47783.57738095238, 49616.3717948718, 51093.517628205125, 52988.801630434784, 55582.01293995859, 57690.24880952381, 58955.36944444444, 61305.794444444444, 64133.81153846154, 66542.6992743106, 69499.69290826285, 72163.66987829615, 73778.35220588234, 75771.86130952381, 78775.03851540617, 81511.60294117648, 84427.58823529413, 88574.66831683168], "n_scenes": 34, "top_entities": [{"label": "matty", "count": 371, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "cranford", "count": 164, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "peter", "count": 114, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "jenkyns", "count": 110, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "martha", "count": 105, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "jamieson", "count": 99, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "glenmire", "count": 64, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "forrester", "count": 53, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "jessie", "count": 50, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "brown", "count": 50, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "deborah", "count": 48, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "matilda", "count": 35, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "pole", "count": 32, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "hoggins", "count": 31, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "johnson", "count": 26, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "fitz-adam", "count": 26, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "jamieson’s", "count": 25, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "mulliner", "count": 22, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "holbrook", "count": 19, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "signor brunoni", "count": 17, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "barker", "count": 16, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "jenny", "count": 15, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "india", "count": 15, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "jem", "count": 15, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "betty", "count": 14, "type": "PERSON"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 90536.67433716859, "activity": 0.04897659814986156}, {"token": 90999.5407703852, "activity": 0.04897147915212562}, {"token": 36149.86843421711, "activity": 0.046358009859031324}, {"token": 40269.37968984492, "activity": 0.045807507899606914}, {"token": 88592.63531765883, "activity": 0.040593430940901475}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 34, "edges": 431, "scene_entity_counts": [14, 14, 14, 9, 14, 22, 10, 16, 12, 14, 12, 27, 16, 22, 20, 12, 12, 11, 11, 16, 14, 11, 14, 17, 17, 25, 9, 13, 6, 12, 16, 15, 20, 37]}, "elapsed_s": 7.94}
{"slug": "Crime_and_Punishment_Fyodor_Dostoyevsky", "title": "Crime and Punishment Fyodor Dostoyevsky", "language": "en", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 270860, "n_unique_entities": 129, "n_entity_mentions": 4099, "sigma": 677.15, "target_scenes": 60, "detected_scene_boundaries": [2095.994652406417, 4653.6209150326795, 8189.544444444445, 12031.896875, 16026.36314006024, 19319.397250975733, 23809.716700201207, 30296.953896103892, 36306.2904040404, 40185.16666666667, 42746.7398989899, 47060.49110671937, 51544.459288537546, 56082.20481283423, 60549.02054154995, 63996.95979986197, 67474.17274247491, 70508.59875930521, 73271.83518724509, 78632.4361430396, 83850.57407407407, 88411.57882882882, 93207.54677754678, 95761.0244458931, 98000.89564446197, 101263.11029156542, 106677.31470488466, 112395.33680955121, 117642.42846907093, 123080.37006861065, 129677.82651515151, 135283.45221088437, 138274.3292942177, 143832.60289634147, 149352.3057149689, 152731.3766968326, 156752.72596153847, 160830.06845238095, 164262.19129720854, 168824.444273399, 173561.34997795415, 177228.69007535675, 181886.88951893177, 186339.34116863343, 189473.76853281853, 191913.73679653677, 195195.01893939392, 198266.46173469388, 201028.87595038017, 206450.3533182504, 211323.94743589743, 213783.5490636704, 217567.9362782823, 222414.40236612703, 226915.72705627704, 231797.67023809522, 237256.81217948717, 243278.71320688445, 250440.37537804662, 255810.7554112554, 259659.1154945683, 263522.8858384567, 266894.1621187801], "n_scenes": 64, "top_entities": [{"label": "raskolnikov", "count": 774, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "sonia", "count": 344, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "dounia", "count": 312, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "svidrigaïlov", "count": 194, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "razumihin", "count": 156, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "katerina ivanovna", "count": 147, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "pyotr petrovitch", "count": 140, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "rodya", "count": 125, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "porfiry", "count": 113, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "pulcheria alexandrovna", "count": 110, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "avdotya romanovna", "count": 104, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "luzhin", "count": 95, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "nastasya", "count": 83, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "zossimov", "count": 82, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "porfiry petrovitch", "count": 75, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "rodion romanovitch", "count": 68, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "zametov", "count": 66, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "lebeziatnikov", "count": 64, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "marfa petrovna", "count": 61, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "sofya semyonovna", "count": 60, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "petersburg", "count": 47, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "lizaveta", "count": 47, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "amalia ivanovna", "count": 33, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "polenka", "count": 29, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "german", "count": 27, "type": "NORP"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 147962.9954977489, "activity": 0.03262447370965686}, {"token": 265168.1155577789, "activity": 0.03050191035387426}, {"token": 99183.9859929965, "activity": 0.030391774006251003}, {"token": 120321.5567783892, "activity": 0.028190593403205854}, {"token": 190780.12606303152, "activity": 0.0279309528115873}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 64, "edges": 749, "scene_entity_counts": [12, 5, 6, 10, 10, 9, 16, 13, 12, 3, 3, 6, 5, 14, 10, 11, 11, 22, 9, 22, 14, 15, 15, 8, 12, 13, 16, 23, 15, 23, 14, 16, 15, 14, 28, 14, 15, 11, 12, 11, 11, 13, 24, 12, 19, 13, 16, 13, 17, 8, 15, 15, 18, 16, 12, 14, 15, 21, 24, 18, 12, 17, 15, 7]}, "elapsed_s": 22.45}
{"slug": "Cynthias_Chauffeur_Louis_Tracy", "title": "Cynthias Chauffeur Louis Tracy", "language": "en", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 109614, "n_unique_entities": 130, "n_entity_mentions": 3062, "sigma": 274.035, "target_scenes": 36, "detected_scene_boundaries": [2584.7513611615245, 4634.02722323049, 5990.2633443552195, 7505.48398741207, 9946.85641891892, 12824.798611111111, 15071.351851851852, 16983.985185185185, 19136.763312368974, 22673.878624022087, 26182.537175452402, 28572.730050933787, 31438.82955465587, 34390.6360780065, 37511.585345405765, 41613.69285714286, 44834.993693693694, 47583.112027027026, 50214.613735632185, 51685.463259441705, 53400.02683150183, 55673.68377110694, 58104.331969743755, 62188.615506329115, 65835.73349056604, 67944.22654612159, 70472.48449391172, 73052.16018835615, 76035.3731617647, 79195.99347426472, 81578.81466490965, 83672.99060240964, 85619.78615384616, 87126.43166109253, 89459.37335771366, 93223.91007268951, 97024.6253968254, 100276.65317460318, 103545.26212121212, 106987.32081686429], "n_scenes": 41, "top_entities": [{"label": "medenham", "count": 387, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "cynthia", "count": 385, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "devar", "count": 256, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "vanrenen", "count": 167, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "dale", "count": 165, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "marigny", "count": 127, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "fitzroy", "count": 118, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "london", "count": 86, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "mercury", "count": 76, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "bristol", "count": 73, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "simmonds", "count": 68, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "frenchman", "count": 62, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "hereford", "count": 60, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "american", "count": 42, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "earl", "count": 41, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "leland", "count": 39, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "england", "count": 38, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "paris", "count": 38, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "fairholme", "count": 36, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "smith", "count": 35, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "viscount medenham", "count": 31, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "french", "count": 28, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "cynthia vanrenen", "count": 20, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "bournemouth", "count": 20, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "porthcawl", "count": 20, "type": "GPE"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 90421.12906453227, "activity": 0.05501656832145425}, {"token": 49131.189594797404, "activity": 0.0537737559025608}, {"token": 59549.633816908456, "activity": 0.04984433931588798}, {"token": 102265.25512756378, "activity": 0.049652017418757376}, {"token": 91408.1395697849, "activity": 0.04754497687464503}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 41, "edges": 869, "scene_entity_counts": [27, 15, 12, 17, 20, 27, 31, 18, 18, 24, 34, 20, 24, 19, 24, 26, 24, 25, 39, 20, 26, 20, 25, 38, 13, 12, 20, 25, 33, 28, 22, 27, 28, 22, 26, 41, 22, 21, 37, 38, 11]}, "elapsed_s": 10.17}
{"slug": "Daintys_Cruel_Rivals_Or_The_Fatal_Birthday_Mrs_Alex_McVeigh_Miller", "title": "Daintys Cruel Rivals Or The Fatal Birthday Mrs Alex McVeigh Miller", "language": "en", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 70743, "n_unique_entities": 43, "n_entity_mentions": 1006, "sigma": 176.8575, "target_scenes": 23, "detected_scene_boundaries": [4026.897301349325, 6321.210344827587, 8784.66923076923, 11597.533936651584, 15992.254289215687, 20618.80386904762, 24420.75064935065, 29022.40606060606, 34478.90253279059, 39095.64712153518, 42511.60317460318, 45734.13174603175, 50602.800996677746, 56812.802583979326, 61614.548792270536, 65446.817006053934], "n_scenes": 17, "top_entities": [{"label": "ellsworth", "count": 217, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "dainty", "count": 162, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "ela", "count": 111, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "chase", "count": 57, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "olive", "count": 46, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "lovelace ellsworth", "count": 35, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "richmond", "count": 27, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "franklin", "count": 26, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "ailsa", "count": 25, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "sheila", "count": 21, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "sheila kelly", "count": 21, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "platt", "count": 19, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "dainty chase", "count": 18, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "mammy", "count": 16, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "peters", "count": 15, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "white", "count": 15, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "vernon ashley", "count": 14, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "sparks", "count": 13, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "love ellsworth", "count": 11, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "new york", "count": 10, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "craye", "count": 10, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "aunt judith", "count": 8, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "lovelace", "count": 8, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "ela craye", "count": 7, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "west virginia", "count": 7, "type": "GPE"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 37653.570785392694, "activity": 0.03589618751610466}, {"token": 68052.4592296148, "activity": 0.03559159266903165}, {"token": 68406.34617308654, "activity": 0.035276675855316755}, {"token": 2795.706853426713, "activity": 0.0331884510745018}, {"token": 65646.028014007, "activity": 0.03107872896855387}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 17, "edges": 187, "scene_entity_counts": [14, 9, 9, 8, 11, 13, 15, 18, 11, 16, 14, 10, 13, 14, 10, 14, 31]}, "elapsed_s": 6.08}
{"slug": "Doctor_Cupid_A_Novel_Rhoda_Broughton", "title": "Doctor Cupid A Novel Rhoda Broughton", "language": "en", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 163463, "n_unique_entities": 75, "n_entity_mentions": 2455, "sigma": 408.6575, "target_scenes": 54, "detected_scene_boundaries": [3038.9988216810684, 5067.75, 8149.077894736842, 10952.45, 12494.626153846155, 16003.496153846154, 20365.65, 23373.634615384617, 25889.46480406386, 28503.41352201258, 30867.411458333336, 32826.08284198113, 35371.25471698113, 38059.09090909091, 40984.69276094276, 45745.011687917424, 49923.128017883755, 52611.91979472141, 55262.12096774194, 57650.83870967742, 60846.99562602515, 64400.063113291704, 66904.69795321637, 69358.1458937198, 71800.48478260869, 74187.53214285715, 76658.10119047618, 80341.86904761905, 84855.61734693877, 87695.6356396217, 89625.98450889914, 90981.38694792353, 92281.81779053085, 96112.88586479367, 100800.18426051561, 104063.02440191388, 107390.28947368421, 109710.21052631579, 112229.11111111111, 115586.73611111111, 118254.125, 120325.14285714286, 123652.38704318937, 127168.75362000878, 129700.10699493787, 131931.68922764226, 135088.02189922478, 138866.725104353, 142161.87551695615, 145142.43199651263, 146984.28885135136, 148873.1625, 151366.4343023256, 154412.10930232558, 156975.70263157896, 159921.4454887218], "n_scenes": 57, "top_entities": [{"label": "peggy", "count": 503, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "prue", "count": 465, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "betty", "count": 188, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "margaret", "count": 156, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "freddy", "count": 154, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "evans", "count": 91, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "talbot", "count": 67, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "harborough", "count": 58, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "franky", "count": 51, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "john talbot", "count": 44, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "lily", "count": 42, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "roupell", "count": 41, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "jacob", "count": 31, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "ducane", "count": 28, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "london", "count": 27, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "hartley", "count": 27, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "john", "count": 26, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "milady", "count": 26, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "lambton", "count": 25, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "harboroughs", "count": 21, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "judas", "count": 21, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "oxford", "count": 20, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "freddy ducane", "count": 19, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "the red house", "count": 18, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "hartleys", "count": 18, "type": "PERSON"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 2044.297148574287, "activity": 0.0349701183357904}, {"token": 99598.15707853927, "activity": 0.03058412197272097}, {"token": 132715.7708854427, "activity": 0.028791897283915072}, {"token": 53478.813406703346, "activity": 0.0281030955440141}, {"token": 143918.5192596298, "activity": 0.02705229132398493}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 57, "edges": 674, "scene_entity_counts": [17, 12, 15, 12, 9, 21, 18, 20, 16, 14, 12, 11, 20, 21, 8, 13, 16, 13, 20, 17, 19, 16, 13, 6, 20, 15, 8, 6, 10, 14, 9, 9, 9, 13, 26, 20, 9, 13, 8, 5, 4, 6, 4, 18, 9, 12, 21, 15, 15, 15, 5, 9, 12, 20, 15, 8, 8]}, "elapsed_s": 13.51}
{"slug": "Dr_Mabuse_der_Spieler_Norbert_Jacques", "title": "Dr Mabuse der Spieler Norbert Jacques", "language": "de", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 98462, "n_unique_entities": 151, "n_entity_mentions": 1558, "sigma": 246.155, "target_scenes": 32, "detected_scene_boundaries": [5605.219512195122, 9352.867660343269, 12637.505291005291, 15764.28380952381, 19103.213333333333, 24916.651250000003, 30539.560235507248, 36762.68860992039, 42031.0106048053, 46082.459507523934, 51416.91554467564, 54889.2514619883, 57510.90681003584, 60882.25741063645, 65039.29231280461, 69100.47749374827, 72695.13445484443, 76396.31375266524, 80542.2469555035, 83808.33843571006, 86066.96238612989, 89209.33483890395, 92803.59071869488], "n_scenes": 24, "top_entities": [{"label": "wenk", "count": 363, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "hull", "count": 56, "type": "PER"}, {"label": "mabuse", "count": 52, "type": "MISC"}, {"label": "spoerri", "count": 42, "type": "PER"}, {"label": "münchen", "count": 41, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "told", "count": 38, "type": "PER"}, {"label": "georg", "count": 34, "type": "PER"}, {"label": "carozza", "count": 24, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "weltmann", "count": 23, "type": "PER"}, {"label": "augenblick", "count": 20, "type": "MISC"}, {"label": "schweiz", "count": 20, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "basch", "count": 20, "type": "MISC"}, {"label": "konstanz", "count": 20, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "mabuses", "count": 19, "type": "PER"}, {"label": "zeit", "count": 17, "type": "MISC"}, {"label": "kommissar", "count": 17, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "mann", "count": 16, "type": "PER"}, {"label": "andern", "count": 15, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "tages", "count": 15, "type": "MISC"}, {"label": "schachen", "count": 15, "type": "MISC"}, {"label": "wenks", "count": 14, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "schramms", "count": 14, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "berlin", "count": 13, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "balling", "count": 13, "type": "MISC"}, {"label": "karstens", "count": 11, "type": "PER"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 41817.60330165082, "activity": 0.04081599389822974}, {"token": 85162.11555777889, "activity": 0.03545424374926817}, {"token": 70976.63881940971, "activity": 0.031068665703610724}, {"token": 63292.838919459726, "activity": 0.030512167981391183}, {"token": 8570.39219609805, "activity": 0.03041296760178097}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 24, "edges": 494, "scene_entity_counts": [20, 22, 17, 18, 37, 45, 31, 28, 39, 30, 27, 15, 16, 18, 34, 33, 18, 26, 38, 26, 29, 26, 25, 27]}, "elapsed_s": 9.14}
{"slug": "Dracula_Bram_Stoker", "title": "Dracula Bram Stoker", "language": "en", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 205113, "n_unique_entities": 143, "n_entity_mentions": 2366, "sigma": 512.7825, "target_scenes": 60, "detected_scene_boundaries": [2875.331597222222, 6545.284722222223, 9830.223214285714, 13857.346611721612, 19440.082956259426, 24470.730392156864, 28333.740476190476, 31892.01825396825, 34687.295893719805, 37635.57367149759, 41471.05065359477, 45959.202087286525, 50752.110322580644, 55193.9, 58701.75105263158, 62140.7479757085, 65006.718227424746, 67575.07153690596, 70517.28023255814, 73933.9375, 78982.0286764706, 84141.24474789915, 89424.44150246306, 94720.03008789723, 98972.84087481146, 102910.09871794871, 107259.0388888889, 111999.75163398693, 115613.81512605042, 119290.13882163035, 122387.0197740113, 124478.21568627452, 126775.63845050216, 129169.47484756098, 132043.09375, 135945.42905405405, 139344.3187599364, 142260.91470588234, 146198.17777777778, 150594.69444444444, 153870.70512820513, 155568.17639257293, 157492.6571618037, 160591.74145299144, 163368.93055555556, 166313.61111111112, 169352.11009485094, 173103.90731707317, 177309.60909090907, 180396.0688131313, 183336.13408119656, 186442.14102564103, 189836.21461187216, 192108.8336594912, 196543.83116883115, 201818.26767676766], "n_scenes": 57, "top_entities": [{"label": "van helsing", "count": 276, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "lucy", "count": 264, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "jonathan", "count": 156, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "arthur", "count": 132, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "harker", "count": 109, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "seward", "count": 65, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "london", "count": 64, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "john", "count": 64, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "mina", "count": 61, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "quincey", "count": 56, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "morris", "count": 48, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "renfield", "count": 46, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "seward’s diary", "count": 36, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "whitby", "count": 35, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "godalming", "count": 32, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "on:--", "count": 30, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "carfax", "count": 24, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "varna", "count": 23, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "quincey morris", "count": 21, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "un-dead", "count": 21, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "dracula", "count": 20, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "galatz", "count": 18, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "van helsing’s", "count": 17, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "madam mina", "count": 17, "type": "FAC"}, {"label": "czarina catherine", "count": 17, "type": "PERSON"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 513.0365182591296, "activity": 0.033204723414651804}, {"token": 190849.5847923962, "activity": 0.029850230505359614}, {"token": 182641.00050025014, "activity": 0.02690630054457876}, {"token": 181512.32016008004, "activity": 0.0228538120808402}, {"token": 93167.43171585794, "activity": 0.022546134301987552}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 57, "edges": 819, "scene_entity_counts": [29, 12, 7, 15, 21, 12, 12, 15, 12, 12, 18, 8, 11, 26, 12, 18, 12, 9, 12, 12, 20, 21, 14, 27, 18, 23, 16, 17, 13, 17, 18, 17, 10, 18, 17, 17, 17, 17, 19, 17, 16, 9, 11, 14, 20, 14, 16, 29, 21, 14, 24, 19, 25, 29, 29, 18, 16]}, "elapsed_s": 17.19}
{"slug": "Ecce_Homo_Friedrich_Wilhelm_Nietzsche", "title": "Ecce Homo Friedrich Wilhelm Nietzsche", "language": "en", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 61936, "n_unique_entities": 62, "n_entity_mentions": 626, "sigma": 154.84, "target_scenes": 20, "detected_scene_boundaries": [3188.1911764705883, 5782.84375, 7756.90625, 9572.79326923077, 11598.337912087913, 14550.776954177898, 19203.48015614834, 22829.810344827587, 25548.8, 28173.226470588233, 29727.39705882353, 31501.06582633053, 33805.332080200504, 36453.66866028708, 39551.61363636364, 42856.93181818182, 46086.40909090909, 48323.23409090909, 49899.7, 53053.88690476191, 55920.26190476191, 57392.125, 59967.0], "n_scenes": 24, "top_entities": [{"label": "zarathustra", "count": 82, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "german", "count": 73, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "wagner", "count": 56, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "nietzsche", "count": 47, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "germans", "count": 43, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "germany", "count": 22, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "christianity", "count": 17, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "dionysian", "count": 17, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "schopenhauer", "count": 14, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "christian", "count": 13, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "thou", "count": 13, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "europe", "count": 12, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "greek", "count": 11, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "french", "count": 9, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "dionysus", "count": 8, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "turin", "count": 7, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "christians", "count": 6, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "truth", "count": 6, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "ye", "count": 6, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "genoa", "count": 6, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "leipzig", "count": 6, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "paris", "count": 6, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "fate", "count": 5, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "bayreuth", "count": 5, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "russian", "count": 5, "type": "NORP"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 16359.019509754879, "activity": 0.04621886725796584}, {"token": 43593.06903451726, "activity": 0.039619048650300775}, {"token": 45080.25262631316, "activity": 0.03537034544430575}, {"token": 44429.60980490245, "activity": 0.03511175858679356}, {"token": 30859.059529764883, "activity": 0.03266565225398706}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 24, "edges": 192, "scene_entity_counts": [15, 9, 9, 3, 8, 18, 19, 19, 10, 15, 12, 13, 14, 9, 8, 10, 23, 9, 7, 5, 6, 6, 3, 4]}, "elapsed_s": 5.36}
{"slug": "Eloisa_Jean-Jacques_Rousseau", "title": "Eloisa Jean-Jacques Rousseau", "language": "en", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 391417, "n_unique_entities": 100, "n_entity_mentions": 2135, "sigma": 978.5425, "target_scenes": 60, "detected_scene_boundaries": [6423.516406562625, 14380.914705882355, 21388.632456140353, 27504.603668261563, 31882.42787878788, 35379.272352941174, 40187.81568627451, 47013.71363636364, 54420.196969696975, 59601.63541666667, 65435.849702380954, 75508.43864468865, 84752.04380341881, 89761.12247474748, 93115.4196969697, 96792.87948717948, 102714.56837606838, 109371.30555555556, 115173.13768115942, 122457.15217391305, 132595.07104037266, 141698.68154761905, 149972.0833333333, 158595.5732758621, 164473.50596816977, 171516.10769230768, 180257.89090909093, 187777.82090909092, 194633.43833333332, 201255.41666666666, 208174.05407801416, 217776.28805237316, 226130.27802197804, 231507.2357142857, 236232.71666666667, 240355.50215053762, 244860.0465949821, 249863.34188034188, 256212.077991453, 261208.37752525252, 265738.25946969696, 271371.61378205125, 275391.3846153846, 280078.36363636365, 286873.86363636365, 294761.6847826087, 301973.73741418764, 307328.62207602337, 311204.08506944444, 315228.5621366279, 321228.3590116279, 329299.58669354836, 338900.21537001897, 345614.1334841629, 348893.4304029304, 356651.49945887446, 366228.67599778273, 372484.0780956848, 379203.6967948718, 386313.9938596491], "n_scenes": 61, "top_entities": [{"label": "eloisa", "count": 697, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "wolmar", "count": 228, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "orbe", "count": 103, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "clara", "count": 103, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "paris", "count": 76, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "french", "count": 72, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "thou", "count": 42, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "r.", "count": 39, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "st. preux", "count": 35, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "fanny", "count": 34, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "geneva", "count": 29, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "clarens", "count": 27, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "france", "count": 25, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "london", "count": 24, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "laura", "count": 23, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "harriot", "count": 22, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "italian", "count": 21, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "italy", "count": 20, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "rome", "count": 20, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "christian", "count": 19, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "england", "count": 16, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "meillerie", "count": 16, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "europe", "count": 14, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "providence", "count": 14, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "adieu", "count": 13, "type": "PERSON"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 304869.7908954477, "activity": 0.018531009909463287}, {"token": 128644.47823911955, "activity": 0.013672108097505296}, {"token": 375359.915957979, "activity": 0.013598995178309288}, {"token": 1958.0590295147572, "activity": 0.013346440741314716}, {"token": 124924.16608304152, "activity": 0.012094222044983862}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 61, "edges": 592, "scene_entity_counts": [20, 16, 7, 4, 7, 5, 9, 7, 10, 16, 13, 18, 11, 8, 6, 6, 9, 10, 10, 19, 29, 18, 14, 7, 6, 11, 6, 4, 15, 11, 17, 20, 15, 14, 8, 2, 8, 6, 7, 13, 8, 8, 4, 6, 8, 7, 17, 15, 6, 8, 14, 18, 24, 10, 5, 9, 15, 9, 11, 26, 22]}, "elapsed_s": 29.85}
{"slug": "Emily_Brontë_A_Mary_F_Robinson", "title": "Emily Brontë A Mary F Robinson", "language": "en", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 90011, "n_unique_entities": 133, "n_entity_mentions": 1834, "sigma": 225.0275, "target_scenes": 30, "detected_scene_boundaries": [2648.25569358178, 6766.603468757425, 12748.81206088993, 17329.798500881836, 19482.59989461006, 22946.01379974326, 26469.585655314757, 28902.031862745098, 31506.625938673344, 35664.934018646905, 39321.18349422378, 41313.54428264502, 44329.69811676083, 49276.24501915709, 54298.951451905625, 58313.00305110603, 63536.755682684976, 68535.15559210526, 72373.62071078431, 75848.30196078432, 79439.93448275863, 83320.07019704435, 86691.5623100304], "n_scenes": 24, "top_entities": [{"label": "charlotte", "count": 224, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "branwell", "count": 175, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "heathcliff", "count": 102, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "anne", "count": 90, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "haworth", "count": 85, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "bronte", "count": 79, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "catharine", "count": 62, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "emily", "count": 56, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "emily bronte", "count": 43, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "london", "count": 25, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "gaskell", "count": 25, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "french", "count": 25, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "cathy", "count": 25, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "shirley", "count": 23, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "wuthering heights", "count": 23, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "brussels", "count": 23, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "earnshaw", "count": 22, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "maria", "count": 21, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "ellen", "count": 21, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "heger", "count": 18, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "hindley", "count": 17, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "linton", "count": 17, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "edgar", "count": 16, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "hareton", "count": 16, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "yorkshire", "count": 15, "type": "PERSON"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 360.22011005502753, "activity": 0.05645306568198878}, {"token": 74160.31515757879, "activity": 0.04928133060124044}, {"token": 32915.11255627814, "activity": 0.04857123139636354}, {"token": 88253.92696348175, "activity": 0.04834260186472841}, {"token": 27736.94847423712, "activity": 0.045937988904912956}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 24, "edges": 436, "scene_entity_counts": [35, 31, 30, 29, 16, 22, 22, 29, 15, 30, 24, 17, 17, 17, 18, 23, 30, 23, 19, 20, 33, 22, 15, 32]}, "elapsed_s": 8.14}
{"slug": "Erotica_Romana_Johann_Wolfgang_von_Goethe", "title": "Erotica Romana Johann Wolfgang von Goethe", "language": "en", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 8814, "n_unique_entities": 7, "n_entity_mentions": 53, "sigma": 22.035, "target_scenes": 3, "detected_scene_boundaries": [2979.08850931677, 5282.29981884058], "n_scenes": 3, "top_entities": [{"label": "rome", "count": 17, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "cupid", "count": 14, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "jupiter", "count": 7, "type": "LOC"}, {"label": "midas", "count": 5, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "werther", "count": 4, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "juno", "count": 3, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "hercules", "count": 3, "type": "PERSON"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 361.51375687843927, "activity": 0.054045221505162146}, {"token": 2812.7533766883444, "activity": 0.05121582269150439}, {"token": 767.1145572786394, "activity": 0.04522550035442999}, {"token": 7662.328164082041, "activity": 0.037837550005866805}, {"token": 3209.5367683841923, "activity": 0.03561789304708783}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 3, "edges": 7, "scene_entity_counts": [5, 4, 5]}, "elapsed_s": 0.96}
{"slug": "Forest_Days_A_Romance_of_Old_Times_G_P_R_James", "title": "Forest Days A Romance of Old Times G P R James", "language": "en", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 221501, "n_unique_entities": 161, "n_entity_mentions": 3928, "sigma": 553.7525, "target_scenes": 60, "detected_scene_boundaries": [3577.0280748663104, 8914.45814479638, 13287.93300248139, 16568.817617866007, 20787.16317016317, 26667.94155844156, 32614.680272108842, 37248.46219851577, 40969.621212121216, 44579.42324561404, 47733.708502024296, 51438.236497545004, 54969.124486748784, 57243.4414747807, 60861.4765625, 65218.953125, 70043.72527689874, 75144.26665739324, 79644.12565303549, 83399.44732401156, 87224.72526737968, 90578.72242424241, 94559.15333333332, 99176.6301234568, 103424.33129992738, 108471.14742647059, 113507.64301470589, 118171.54602396514, 121804.7151416122, 126150.52663706992, 131622.2522615663, 135194.29334895458, 137014.52488558352, 141019.57002022245, 147141.95243128965, 151894.02201704547, 154570.95629222973, 158187.40425803163, 162187.16998284735, 164554.97272727272, 167530.83333333334, 170686.20164884138, 172881.92892156861, 176304.35833333334, 180285.63155737706, 182787.89901020724, 184575.07129898405, 186428.97602925243, 188382.45580378824, 190265.13862068966, 193569.6783870968, 197346.1698156682, 201459.81108374384, 205556.82536945812, 208857.72337662338, 213243.33766233767, 217808.66379310345], "n_scenes": 58, "top_entities": [{"label": "hugh", "count": 301, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "lucy", "count": 276, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "hugh de monthermer", "count": 250, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "earl", "count": 244, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "richard de ashby", "count": 211, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "edward", "count": 140, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "de montfort", "count": 116, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "nottingham", "count": 108, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "robin", "count": 104, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "robin hood", "count": 87, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "kate", "count": 87, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "ashby", "count": 80, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "tangel", "count": 70, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "guy de margan", "count": 70, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "england", "count": 63, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "richard", "count": 61, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "alured de ashby", "count": 54, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "monthermer", "count": 47, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "sherwood", "count": 44, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "lindwell", "count": 43, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "gloucester", "count": 43, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "alured", "count": 40, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "lucy de ashby", "count": 39, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "hereford", "count": 39, "type": "FAC"}, {"label": "mortimer", "count": 37, "type": "PERSON"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 77785.39269634818, "activity": 0.03270443823649996}, {"token": 138395.947973987, "activity": 0.03202970924897798}, {"token": 88865.93296648323, "activity": 0.030195982143358176}, {"token": 45984.24212106053, "activity": 0.029699286661594413}, {"token": 105597.54877438719, "activity": 0.029662946193103768}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 58, "edges": 1198, "scene_entity_counts": [10, 18, 15, 20, 20, 32, 32, 22, 35, 25, 24, 25, 15, 15, 9, 11, 23, 32, 33, 23, 25, 30, 25, 25, 29, 40, 34, 34, 15, 37, 32, 26, 15, 30, 36, 18, 23, 24, 15, 21, 16, 20, 24, 25, 19, 22, 21, 13, 25, 14, 19, 20, 25, 29, 23, 18, 21, 32]}, "elapsed_s": 18.49}
{"slug": "Four_Arthurian_Romances_Chrétien_de_Troyes", "title": "Four Arthurian Romances Chrétien de Troyes", "language": "en", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 239503, "n_unique_entities": 154, "n_entity_mentions": 2279, "sigma": 598.7575, "target_scenes": 60, "detected_scene_boundaries": [2379.563404958678, 4264.900181818182, 10255.068181818182, 18050.521739130432, 22478.3134057971, 26257.109848484848, 29375.38961038961, 31478.133928571428, 33420.39583333333, 36913.120833333334, 41599.7375, 46071.4, 51991.91666666667, 57668.74166666667, 62536.75119047619, 67302.8386904762, 72667.9671511628, 77083.44750830566, 79806.57619047619, 83817.37988505747, 88435.73746081506, 92607.67581475129, 95501.08490566038, 98052.14864864864, 101826.89864864864, 105901.23571428572, 109029.1857142857, 113426.46785714285, 119272.58861185983, 124180.93186582808, 128108.86111111111, 130924.09782608696, 133572.0401337793, 136095.233974359, 139811.4527777778, 143702.66786786786, 147573.47550675675, 152459.86875, 156312.82857142854, 160366.47402597402, 163802.61363636365, 166698.7681818182, 170981.15967741935, 174539.3287250384, 178144.9123809524, 184172.60583333333, 190864.7125, 196036.73333333334, 200809.9895833333, 206181.4895833333, 210523.362745098, 215325.25163398692, 219539.17874396135, 222095.44804716285, 227304.45494005788, 233441.5841042893, 237197.04441846872], "n_scenes": 58, "top_entities": [{"label": "yvain", "count": 161, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "lancelot", "count": 153, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "gawain", "count": 137, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "cligés", "count": 116, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "kay", "count": 84, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "alexander", "count": 83, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "chrétien", "count": 78, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "thou", "count": 78, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "enide", "count": 69, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "king", "count": 68, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "arthur", "count": 66, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "queen", "count": 64, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "john", "count": 50, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "french", "count": 43, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "erec", "count": 39, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "tristan", "count": 28, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "britain", "count": 25, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "greece", "count": 25, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "fenice", "count": 25, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "ford", "count": 24, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "paris", "count": 23, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "guivret", "count": 23, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "thessala", "count": 22, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "meleagant", "count": 22, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "foerster", "count": 20, "type": "PERSON"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 2276.407203601801, "activity": 0.03750697063584008}, {"token": 718.8654327163581, "activity": 0.03667082625984726}, {"token": 4552.814407203602, "activity": 0.03498148085353517}, {"token": 63739.40170085042, "activity": 0.032370175507445656}, {"token": 121009.01450725363, "activity": 0.03175056931922439}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 58, "edges": 661, "scene_entity_counts": [40, 27, 50, 18, 19, 16, 4, 2, 3, 3, 12, 9, 14, 10, 39, 57, 15, 16, 10, 6, 25, 11, 12, 6, 10, 18, 15, 10, 11, 64, 4, 7, 4, 2, 6, 11, 8, 5, 5, 5, 11, 4, 2, 11, 6, 44, 10, 7, 9, 6, 8, 11, 5, 8, 12, 16, 8, 28]}, "elapsed_s": 19.78}
{"slug": "Frankenstein_or_the_modern_prometheus_Mary_Wollstonecraft_Shelley", "title": "Frankenstein or the modern prometheus Mary Wollstonecraft Shelley", "language": "en", "status": "ok", "n_tokens": 92299, "n_unique_entities": 57, "n_entity_mentions": 681, "sigma": 230.7475, "target_scenes": 30, "detected_scene_boundaries": [1686.7857142857142, 5245.3403361344535, 8852.569659442725, 11200.498803827752, 13598.288277511961, 17185.07780320366, 20956.65543478261, 23330.26824324324, 26440.171814671812, 29921.04978354978, 33119.88437001595, 36083.563157894736, 41424.51875, 45838.0252016129, 47394.70351043643, 50202.361344537814, 52931.30803571429, 54826.46875, 58592.721153846156, 62018.98901098901, 63428.527992277996, 65894.28513513514, 69281.85833333334, 72525.72833333333, 74768.41583333333, 75963.29166666667, 77273.22192028986, 79009.07608695651, 81343.25, 84500.47222222222, 87059.16452991453, 88787.33936651584], "n_scenes": 33, "top_entities": [{"label": "elizabeth", "count": 89, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "justine", "count": 51, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "clerval", "count": 45, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "felix", "count": 41, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "geneva", "count": 36, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "safie", "count": 25, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "frankenstein", "count": 24, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "henry", "count": 23, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "william", "count": 23, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "agatha", "count": 22, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "england", "count": 21, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "victor", "count": 21, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "ingolstadt", "count": 13, "type": "ORG"}, {"label": "arabian", "count": 13, "type": "NORP"}, {"label": "ernest", "count": 13, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "kirwin", "count": 13, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "margaret", "count": 10, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "switzerland", "count": 10, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "paris", "count": 10, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "m. waldman", "count": 9, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "de lacey", "count": 9, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "london", "count": 8, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "turk", "count": 8, "type": "PERSON"}, {"label": "italy", "count": 7, "type": "GPE"}, {"label": "m. krempe", "count": 7, "type": "GPE"}], "peak_activity_positions": [{"token": 48480.69034517258, "activity": 0.046456745430210306}, {"token": 45340.98849424712, "activity": 0.022296912396807613}, {"token": 25163.786893446722, "activity": 0.021901650611205643}, {"token": 24702.06603301651, "activity": 0.020643767784972636}, {"token": 28072.62831415708, "activity": 0.02027001516784609}], "narrative_flow": {"scenes": 33, "edges": 208, "scene_entity_counts": [7, 4, 6, 10, 9, 8, 8, 17, 15, 9, 6, 11, 4, 4, 7, 12, 6, 6, 4, 11, 11, 13, 9, 7, 8, 8, 5, 5, 8, 5, 9, 5, 8]}, "elapsed_s": 7.62}
